const questions = [
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a basic javascript data type ?",
    optionA: "Boolean",
    optionB: "Integer",
    optionC: "String",
    optionD: "Color",
    correctOption: "optionD",
  },

  {
    question:
      "What method combines the text of two strings and returns a new string ?",
    optionA: "add()",
    optionB: "concat()",
    optionC: "combine()",
    optionD: "attach()",
    correctOption: "optionB",
  },

  {
    question: "Arrays in JavaScript can be used to store ________.",
    optionA: "numbers and strings",
    optionB: "other arrays",
    optionC: "booleans",
    optionD: "all of the above",
    correctOption: "optionD",
  },

  {
    question:
      "The condition in an if / else statement is enclosed with ______.",
    optionA: "square brackets",
    optionB: "curly brackets",
    optionC: "quotes",
    optionD: "parenthesis",
    correctOption: "optionC",
  },

  {
    question:
      "A very useful tool used during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is: ",
    optionA: "terminal/bash",
    optionB: "for loops",
    optionC: "JavaScript",
    optionD: "console.log",
    correctOption: "optionD",
  },

  {
    question: "What keyword is used to define a function in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "function",
    optionB: "define",
    optionC: "func",
    optionD: "let",
    correctOption: "optionA",
  },

  {
    question: "What does the `push()` method do in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "Adds an element to the beginning of an array",
    optionB: "Removes an element from the beginning of an array",
    optionC: "Adds an element to the end of an array",
    optionD: "Prints a new line",
    correctOption: "optionC",
  },

  {
    question: "What method removes the last element in an array in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "pop()",
    optionB: "push()",
    optionC: "remove()",
    optionD: "cut()",
    correctOption: "optionA",
  },

  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the `typeof` operator in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "it converts the value of a variable",
    optionB: "it assigns a value of `null`",
    optionC: "it checks if a function will run",
    optionD: "it returns the data type of a value",
    correctOption: "optionD",
  },

  {
    question: "What does the modulus oeprator(%) do?",
    optionA: "performs division",
    optionB: "raises to an exponent",
    optionC: "performs multiplication",
    optionD: "performs division and returns the remainder",
    correctOption: "optionD",
  },
];
